Suns Road
Yomogi Kindergarten! Bazaar today!
Come on over!
Squish?
Could you possibly be, Ioryogi-san?
Who else do you know that looks like this?
Of course it's me!
And would you please get your hand off of me!
Oh, yes sir!
Ko... ba...
Ioryogi-san?
Ioryogi-san!
Yeah?
Are you having a nap in the middle of the street?
If you're sleepy, you should go
home and get into bed.
I am not taking a nap!
Kobato.
What should I do?
Even the most obvious of things
Are always such a challenge
I want to laugh when I'm happy
And sing whenever I want
Is all
They say my dreams will come true someday
But when will "someday" come?
I can't wait forever
On "1, 2, 3!" I'll spread open my arms
And let the light gather around me
Where is it?
Please tell me what I can do
I make the most of getting hurt
And run with all my might
Despite how many dozens of times I fall
And start crying
I surprise myself
In how much I believe in tomorrow
...Mysterious Life Form II.
What in the world is wrong, Ioryogi-san?
Don't you get it?!
Does nothing seem wrong to
you about my appearance?!
Huh?
Um... well...
Ioryogi-san, you are all covered in dirt!
Figure it out!
Anyway, just listen to me!
Yomogi Kindergarten
Bazaar Hall
Looks like heavy clouds today.
It'll be all right!
The clouds will clear, I'm sure.
I certainly hope so.
Ioryogi-san?
I'll bring you something that will surely sell.
Thank you very much!
I said that but do I have something in mind?
No.
I'm just sick and tired of
sitting at the kindergarten
pretending to be a stuffed doll all day long.
I'm going to the bear's place and stuff
myself with some baumkuchen.
Another odd place, as always.
Bear's Baumkuchen Shop
One long!
You got it!
Bear's Baumkuchen Shop
Come during our happy hour
Can I get four cuts please?
Bear's Baumkuchen Shop
Come during our happy hour
Is my short ready yet?
Bear's Baumkuchen Shop
Come during our happy hour
I'd like a half.
Yes, yes. The customer waiting for three
cuts? Thank you for waiting.
Is mine ready yet?
Please wait one more moment,
we're working on it!
Six cuts, ready to go!
How about the long order?
Let me check on that.
Two more minutes.
You look busy.
Hm? Yeah, well it was Zuisho's idea.
A little ingenuity is important.
Let's try more variations next time,
like adding chocolate.
Not a bad idea. Bit by bit, yeah?
You guys are right into this.
At first I didn't know what to expect, but
I think we've got the hang of it now.
Sarcasm doesn't get to you anymore does it?
Huh?
Nothing.
Oh by the way, we've started
delivery service too!
Here.
Right. The Bear's Baumkuchen Shop.
I've been waiting for you. Thanks.
That's all right.
You're not the regular bird. Are you new?
No.
Oh I see. You're a part timer.
I used to do part time work myself.
I had a lot of jobs.
There was one boss that wanted me to
do everything, it was impossible.
You finished talking? Bye.
Oh, by the way...
I once had to go into this
mansion that was like a maze.
It was a really strange place.
There were so many odd rooms.
We're taking a break
You guys are so natural at this, I've completely
forgotten what you used to look like.
I don't mind this body.
Well the hairy part is a bit much, but if
you're careful, you can get used to it.
Being acclimatized is a pretty scary thing.
I feel like I've been like this since I was born.
You know it's hard to believe such
a thing ever happened.
Yeah, to us it was like a bad dream.
It certainly feels like a long, long time ago.
It does.
Think about it logically, we didn't have a chance.
The opponent was just too powerful.
It was totally one sided.
Once we started to crumble, the rest was quick.
I sort of remember stomping on
someone then. I wonder who that was.
That was me!
Oh no! It was you?! I-I'm so sorry!
It's over and done with.
Besides, we weren't in any state of mind to be
getting angry about such things back then.
Woah, don't you start!
No matter how unsatisfied you may be...
after all, rules are rules.
Right now all we can do is bake baumkuchen
cakes and wait for things to settle down.
Right?
We were so close that time.
Hell with that!
This is where you're supposed to repent.
How can you say such a frightening thing?
You must not even think that,
much less talk about it!
He's right. If we poke at Tenkai again, we're not
going to get away with being bears and birds!
I'll probably become a teddy bear and
this guy'll end up being bird feed!
Oh, no! Not that! And that's not fair,
you getting the cute part!
In any case, any trouble, no matter what
the reason, will not be tolerated!
Do you understand?!
Hey, wha?
What do you think you're doing?
Don't go eating my merchandise!
And he only gives me one box to take
with me. Such a stingy bear.
Now...
I've had something sweet to eat,
now I'd like something salty.
Then after having something salty,
I'll have this baumkuchen cake.
Where can I find something
salty? Maybe nowhere.
How about something with soy sauce?
No, I'm in the mood for something salty.
Now let me see...
Something that'll hit me in the stomach...
What are you doing?!
Sorry, that was my fault.
Huh? The ball came back.
That's weird.
Never mind.
Darn kids! Are they all like that?
What could be so fun about fiddling with a ball?
What's this?!
What in the world is going on?
Hey quit that!
I'm not something you'd want to eat!
No! You can't have this! This is my snack!
You're too young for baumkuchen cakes!
If you don't cut that out,
I'll turn you into barbecue...
Hey!
Stop! Hey! Hey!
Darn it! I will not... let go... of this box... if I
have to... put my life... on the... Woah!
Oh, no!
No, not water!
Now this is tough...
Ugh... I feel like I'm about to spit
out something other than fire.
My body is so heavy...
Man, when it rains, it pours, literally.
Smiley Coin Laundry
That'll dry me at once!
Dryers are a lot harder on
the body than I expected.
So...
Where am I?
Is that so?
Yes! That grocery...
In any case, I'm hungry.
No, no, no, no, no. I'm going to get this
home and take my time enjoying it.
It's not like I'm a kid on an errand that couldn't
help himself on the way home.
No, no, no, no, no!
Wh-What is this nice smell?
And what is that mysterious life form?
Welcome to, Mocona Land!
All you little ladies and gentlemen!
Don't get lost having too much fun, now!
Well then, have lots of fun while you're here!
Looks like I've wandered
into some bizarre place.
Oh yes, that great smell.
Everything looks so good!
Woah?! Ow!
Oww... Oh man, I've done it.
I'm sorry about that!
Huh? Hey wait!
Please excuse me for that!
Damn... I'm a stuffed animal but
I'm not a stuffed animal!
I've got to get out of here fast.
Somebody is going to steal
my baumkuchen box.
Huh? What is this place?
Huh? What's he doing?
I'll get you anything you like.
No, no it can't be. Could this be?!
Daddy, get me that!
Okay!
Wh-Why this is...
All right!
A shooting range!
Here you go!
See what I got?
Daddy, I want that blue puppy!
Hm?
Let me see...
Where is it?
That one, right?
Why me?!
Oh too bad!
Aww, I missed it, did I?
No, not "haw, haw, haw"!
I'll get it this time!
Oh no! It's coming straight at me!
Aww, you missed again!
So close!
That's funny. Okay, this time for sure.
Didn't it just move?
Nothing moved, Daddy. You're just a lousy shot.
Shucks. You just watch.
This sort of thing gets me going.
Hang in there Daddy!
Okay, now I'm getting it for sure!
Let's see if you can get it this time.
Damn! You're an adult, don't get so serious!
Just give up will you?
I almost got it!
Let me try!
We'll help you!
Oh no!
He's difficult to hit.
Let me give it a try!
In the olden days, people feared me.
They used to call me "target shooter Kana."
Now who on earth are you?!
Oh, no. You can't have it
unless it falls off the shelf.
What?! What's that you say?!
Okay then! Let's all put our powers together!
No need to put anything together!
Why won't that blue one fall off?!
I will not let myself become a gift
for some child to take home!
Uh.
Hurray!
Congratulations!
Huh?
Where did it go? I can't find it.
Huh? It did just fall, didn't it?
Yeah, I know it did!
You all saw it too, didn't you?
Now that was a terrible experience.
If I get this far, I should be okay...!
So you see, that's what happened.
So you've been running around all this time
because the posters got taken down?
Because nobody was coming to the bazaar.
Well it is a pretty small-scale event.
Even if the posters weren't removed,
you shouldn't be expecting too much from
a bazaar held at some kindergarten.
If this is what it was going to come down to,
perhaps I shouldn't have suggested
the bazaar in the first place.
I don't think so. What's important is that
once you decide to do it, you do it.
Even if you encounter obstacles,
you mustn't give up.
Yes.
Even if you get drenched in water
or shot at by snipers.
Yes?
Oh never mind.
Anyway, the important thing is to see it through.
Don't get discouraged because
you don't have customers.
Yomogi Kindergarten
Bazaar Hall
Kobato! You're back!
You're late!
Look, look at how much we sold!
The weather dolls sold too!
Thanks to you, Kobato, I found a good deal.
How long do you plan to just stand there?
Huh? I-I'm sorry!
Look at the number of guests. We need help.
So get busy and help us out.
Yes!
Kobato?
Thank you so much. If it weren't for you, we
wouldn't have had so many people here today.
Oh! But I...!
Look.
See how much fun everyone is having?
It's all because of you.
Hi Kobato.
Domoto! Thank you for taking the time to come!
You're very welcome. I had a wonderful time.
I'm so glad!
But I would have had a better time if you
handed me my purchases directly.
Oh that's right! I brought some things
I made too. I wonder if they sold.
500 yen each
Nobody bought any.
Well I'm not surprised. Who's going
to want this mysterious life form?
You can't even tell if it's a chicken
or a penguin or a sheep.
Then I'll buy it.
What? Really?
Thank you very much!
It's very unique.
You have an interesting sense of art.
What?
Mmm... a rabbit?
D-Domoto!
Huh?
Today was a lovely day.
I had a horrible day.
Is that so?
Yes that is so! Weren't you listening to me?!
Umm... Is that so?
And your response is still, "is that so?"
Oh well, at least I saved my special
something. All's well that ends well.
As soon as I get home, I am going to indulge!
No, I'm going to slowly enjoy every
bite of my special something!
Special something?
You know!
What do I know?
Huh?
My very special baumkuchen cake! It's gone!
Oh well, I guess we'll just have to go
back to the kindergarten to get it.
Oh, the baumkuchen. That sold immediately.
Huh?
Wha, wha, wha... What did you do that for?!
Ioryogi-san, the " something that
will surely sell" you said.
That baumkuchen cake was that
something, wasn't it?
Thank you so much!
Today's points... 80 for your enthusiasm
in putting on the bazaar, and...
Add to that my disappointment
and the total is minus 300!
WHAT?!
But why?! I don't understand! Why is it my fault
that you're disappointed?! If it is, I apologize!
No apology can help in this case!
Th-Then! I'll give you this cute rabbit that I
especially made so you can feel better!
I don't want it!
Th-Then as a bonus I'll give you two!
I'm telling you, I don't want it!
Then you can also have this
adorable bear and this sheep.
In the first place, I've got no idea what any of
them are! They're all mysterious life forms!
Hey! That's not nice, Ioryogi-san!
Everyone dreams of flying
But they let gravity trick them
Honestly, everyone is already able to fly
I bet the reason that child looks so terribly sad
Is because he
Accidentally lost his shadow somewhere
In that case
If I could just tell you, "Thank you,"
And you laugh and reply, "Thank you"
That exchange would fill you with joy
It would make you feel so happy
There's nothing to worry about
Since we're together
It's strange how I'm crying
Even though I'm happy
Next episode
...Warmth of the Wintry Wind.
Even though I'm happy
Next episode
...Warmth of the Wintry Wind.